Guide to the William Henry Chafe Oral History Collection, 1933-1988 and undated RL.00207
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
William Henry Chafe Oral History collection
1933-1988 and undated
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Chafe, William Henry
RL.00207
5.6 Linear Feet
circa 2930 Items
The William Henry Chafe Oral History Collection spans the years 1933 through 1988, with most of the materials dated between 1972 and 1978. The collection consists mainly of oral history interview tapes and transcripts, but also includes interview notes and research files related to Chafe's book Civilities and Civil Rights: Greensboro, North Carolina, and the Black Struggle for Freedom.
Access Restrictions
The William Henry Chafe Oral History Collection has been restricted due to the absence of release forms transferring intellectual property rights from interviewees or interviewers to researchers using this collection. Researchers are cautioned that the publication of information contained in these interviews may violate the legal rights of interviewees or interviewers. It is the sole responsibility of researchers to secure permission from interviewees or interviewers to publish quotes from either, and to ensure that information gained from research in this collection is not used in any way that violates rights remaining with interviewees, interviewers or their heirs.
Patrons who wish to use this collection must sign a restricted materials research agreement, which may be obtained from any Special Collections reference staff person.
All or portions of this collection may be housed off-site in Duke University's Library Service Center. The library may require up to 48 hours to retrieve these materials for research use.
Please contact Research Services staff before visiting the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library to use this collection.
Provenance
The William Henry Chafe Oral History Collection was donated to Special Collections in 1987 and 2011 by William Henry Chafe.
Collection Overview
The William Henry Chafe Oral History Collection spans the years 1933 through 1988, with most of the materials dated between 1972 and 1978. The collection consists mainly of oral history interview tapes and transcripts, but also includes interview notes and research files related to Chafe's book Civilities and Civil Rights: Greensboro, North Carolina, and the Black Struggle for Freedom.
The interview tapes and transcripts (1972-1978, undated), which comprise the bulk of the collection, include interviews with government officials, participants in the North Carolina civil rights movement of the 1950s and 1960s, and opponents of the movement, including members of the Ku Klux Klan. The few research files in the collection include statistical data related to Greensboro elections (1930s-1950s), notes from the Joan Bluethenthal papers and a report by the North Carolina State Advisory Committee to the United States Commission on Civil Rights on civil disturbances at Dudley High School and North Carolina A&T State University in Greensboro, North Carolina in 1969.
The Audiotapes Series consists of two identical sets (one for preservation, one for use by researchers) of twenty-eight tapes containing oral history interviews. The Printed Material Series includes transcripts and/or notes on 67 oral history interviews, and three research files related to the civil rights movement and local politics in Greensboro.
Beyond the direct oral history materials, there is also a Writings and Research Series. It includes research notes for several chapters of Chafe's book in addition to newspaper clippings addressing topics such as Martin Luther King, Jr.'s assassination and the return of black veterans from the Vietnam War; an assortment of documents regarding the Black Panther Party collected by the Federal Bureau of Investigations' Counter Intelligence Program, and a number of publications produced by other authors. While the materials predominately relate to Greensboro, this series also includes information on civil rights activity in Durham, Chapel Hill, and the Research Triangle at large. The Photographs Series includes fourteen undated photographs.
William H. Chafe's book, Civilities and Civil Rights: Greensboro, North Carolina, and the Black Struggle for Freedom, chronicles the continuing conflict over desegregation in Greensboro in the 1950s and 1960s. Chafe explores the "progressive mystique" that defined the terms of culturally-sanctioned behavior, looking at how civility served to preserve the South's racial order. Within this context, he discusses the city's reaction to the Supreme Court's landmark decision in Brown v. Board of Education in 1954, the Greensboro sit-in movement begun by four college students at North Carolina A&T College in 1960, and the emergence of the Black Power Movement in the late 1960s.
Related Material
Behind the Veil: Documenting African-American Life in the Jim Crow South. 1940-1997 and undated (bulk 1993-1997),
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library, Duke University
African Americans -- Civil rights -- North Carolina; Civil rights -- North Carolina -- Greensboro; Black power -- North Carolina -- History -- 20th century; Black Panther Party; African Americans -- North Carolina -- Greensboro -- Social conditions; North Carolina -- Politics and government -- 1951-; Greensboro (N.C.) -- Race relations; Ku Klux Klan (1915- ) -- North Carolina -- Greensboro; Martin Luther King, Jr. and the Civil Rights Movement; North Carolina A&T State University; Chafe, William Henry; United States Commission on Civil Rights
- Oral histories, 1970-1978; 1
  Scope and Contents
  This series includes oral history interviews as well as 67 transcripts and notes (1972-1978 & undated) related to the civil rights movement in Greensboro, North Carolina. Compact discs of interviews as well as compact disc scans of all transcripts relating to interviews are available, filed by subject. This series also includes audio recordings of William Chafe's notes regarding interviews and his research, as well as transcripts on the Greensboro elections, notes on the papers of Joan Bluethenthal, and a report by the North Carolina State Advisory Committee to the United States Commission on Civil Rights on civil disturbances at Dudley High School and North Carolina A&TState University in Greensboro.
  - Allen, Carolyn, 1974 December 19; 1
    - Carolyn Allen, Side A and B, audiocassette original (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00207-CS-0001)
    - Carolyn Allen, 1 of 2, compact disc use copy (Box 9, Audio-cd RL00207-CD-0132)
    - Carolyn Allen, 2 of 2, compact disc use copy (Box 9, Audio-cd RL00207-CD-0133)
  - Ashby, Warren, 1974 September 25, 1974 October 03; 2
    - Warren Ashby, transcripts and notes (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Warren Ashby, compact disc use copy (Box 10, Data-cd RL00207-CD-0207)
  - Bailey, Tom, 1977 July 09; 3
    - Tom Bailey, Side A and B, audiocassette original (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00207-CS-0002)
    - Tom Bailey, transcripts and notes (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Tom Bailey, compact disc use copy (Box 10, Data-cd RL00207-CD-0207)
    - Tom Bailey, 1 of 2, compact disc use copy (Box 9, Audio-cd RL00207-CD-0134)
    - Tom Bailey, 2 of 2, compact disc use copy (Box 9, Audio-cd RL00207-CD-0135)
  - Bardolph, Richard, 1972 July 11; 4
    - Richard Bardolph, transcripts and notes (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Richard Bardolph, compact disc use copy (Box 10, Data-cd RL00207-CD-0207)
  - Bell, Tartt, 1977 October 13; 5
    - Tartt Bell, Side A and B, audiocassette original (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00207-CS-0003)
    - Tartt Bell, transcripts and notes (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Tartt Bell, compact disc use copy (Box 10, Data-cd RL00207-CD-0207)
    - Tartt Bell, 1 of 2, compact disc use copy (Box 9, Audio-cd RL00207-CD-0136)
    - Tartt Bell, 2 of 2, compact disc use copy (Box 9, Audio-cd RL00207-CD-0137)
  - Bishop, Cecil, Summer 1977, 1977 October 12; 6
    - Rev. Cecil Bishop, transcripts and notes (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Rev. Cecil Bishop, compact disc use copy (Box 10, Data-cd RL00207-CD-0207)
  - Bishop, Cecil, Summer 1977; 7
    - Rev. Cecil Bishop, 1 of 2, audiocassette original (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00207-CS-0004)
    - Rev. Cecil Bishop, 1 of 1, compact disc use copy (Box 9, Audio-cd RL00207-CD-0139)
  - Bishop, Cecil, 1977 October 12; 8
    - Rev. Cecil Bishop, 2 of 2, audiocassette original (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00207-CS-0005)
    - Rev. Cecil Bishop, 1 of 1, compact disc use copy (Box 9, Audio-cd RL00207-CD-0138)
  - Blackwell, Randolph, Undated; 9
    - Randolph Blackwell, transcripts and notes (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Blackwell, Randolph, 1973 March 05, 1973 March 21; 10
    - Randolph Blackwell, transcripts and notes (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Blackwell, Randolph, 1973 March 05, 1973 March 21, Undated; 11
    - Randolph Blackwell, compact disc use copy (Box 10, Data-cd RL00207-CD-0207)
  - Blair, Ezell Jr., 1974 November 27; 13
    - Ezell Blair, Jr., transcripts and notes (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Ezell Blair, Jr., compact disc use copy (Box 10, Data-cd RL00207-CD-0208)
  - Blair, Ezell Sr. and Corene, 1972 March 13; 12
    - Ezell Sr. and Corine Blair, Side A and B, audiocassette original (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00207-CS-0006)
    - Ezell Sr. and Corene Blair, transcripts and notes (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Ezell Sr. and Corene Blair, compact disc use copy (Box 10, Data-cd RL00207-CD-0208)
    - Ezell Sr. and Corene Blair, 1 of 1, compact disc use copy (Box 9, Audio-cd RL00207-CD-0140)
  - Bluethenthal, Joan, 1977 July 13; 14
    - Joan Bluthenthal papers, Side A and B, audiocassette original (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00207-CS-0076)
    - Joan Bluethenthal, transcripts and notes (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Joan Bluethenthal, compact disc use copy (Box 10, Data-cd RL00207-CD-0208)
  - Bluethenthal, Joan, Undated; 15
    - Joan Bluethenthal papers, transcripts and notes (Box 2, Folder 68)
    - Joan Bluethenthal papers, compact disc use copy (Box 10, Data-cd RL00207-CD-0215)
  - Brandon, Lewis, Undated; 16
    - Lewis Brandon, Side A and B, audiocassette original (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00207-CS-0007)
    - Lewis Brandon, transcripts and notes (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Lewis Brandon, compact disc use copy (Box 10, Data-cd RL00207-CD-0208)
    - Lewis Brandon, 1 of 1, compact disc use copy (Box 9, Audio-cd RL00207-CD-0141)
  - Breathett, George, 1974 October 11; 17
    - George Breathett, Side A, audiocassette original (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00207-CS-0008)
    - George Breathett, transcripts and notes (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - George Breathett, compact disc use copy (Box 10, Data-cd RL00207-CD-0208)
    - George Breathett, 1 of 1, compact disc use copy (Box 9, Audio-cd RL00207-CD-0142)
  - Browler, Mrs. Charles, 1974 September 24; 18
    - Mrs. Charles Browler, transcripts and notes (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Mrs. Charles Browler, compact disc use copy (Box 10, Data-cd RL00207-CD-0208)
  - Brown, Sarah Mendenhall, 1974 July 14; 19
    - Sarah Mendenhall Brown, Side B, audiocassette original (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00207-CS-0009)
    - Sarah Mendenhall Brown, transcripts and notes (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Sarah Mendenhall Brown, compact disc use copy (Box 10, Data-cd RL00207-CD-0208)
  - Brown, Walter R. "Dub", 1977 May 20; 20
    - Walter R. "Dub" Brown, Side B, audiocassette original (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00207-CS-0021)
    - Walter R. "Dub" Brown, transcripts and notes (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Walter R. "Dub" Brown, compact disc use copy (Box 10, Data-cd RL00207-CD-0208)
    - Walter R. "Dub" Brown, 1 of 1, compact disc use copy (Box 9, Audio-cd RL00207-CD-0143)
    - Walter R. "Dub" Brown, 1 of 2, compact disc use copy (Box 9, Audio-cd RL00207-CD-0161)
  - Chavis, Vance, 1973 May 20; 21
    - Vance Chavis, 2 of 2, audiocassette original (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00207-CS-0011)
    - Vance Chavis, transcripts and notes (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Vance Chavis, compact disc use copy (Box 10, Data-cd RL00207-CD-0209)
    - Vance Chavis, 1 of 1, compact disc use copy (Box 9, Audio-cd RL00207-CD-0144)
    - Vance Chavis, 1 of 2, compact disc use copy (Box 9, Audio-cd RL00207-CD-0145)
    - Vance Chavis, 2 of 2, compact disc use copy (Box 9, Audio-cd RL00207-CD-0146)
  - Chavis, Vance, 1974 October 19; 22
    - Vance Chavis, 1 of 2, audiocassette original (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00207-CS-0010)
  - Coley, Nell, 1974 October 15; 23
    - Nell Coley, Side A and B, audiocassette original (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00207-CS-0084)
    - Nell Coley, transcripts and notes (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Nell Coley, compact disc use copy (Box 10, Data-cd RL00207-CD-0209)
  - Davis, Charles, Undated; 24
    - Charles Davis, transcripts and notes (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Charles Davis, compact disc use copy (Box 10, Data-cd RL00207-CD-0209)
  - Dawson, Eddie, 1977 May 26; 25
    - Eddie Dawson, Side A and B, audiocassette original (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00207-CS-0012)
    - Eddie Dawson, Side A and B, audiocassette original (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00207-CS-0019)
    - Eddie Dawson, transcripts and notes (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Eddie Dawson, compact disc use copy (Box 10, Data-cd RL00207-CD-0209)
    - Eddie Dawson, 1 of 2, compact disc use copy (Box 9, Audio-cd RL00207-CD-0147)
    - Eddie Dawson, 2 of 2, compact disc use copy (Box 9, Audio-cd RL00207-CD-0148)
    - Eddie Dawson, 1 of 2, compact disc use copy (Box 9, Audio-cd RL00207-CD-0157)
    - Eddie Dawson, 2 of 2, compact disc use copy (Box 9, Audio-cd RL00207-CD-0158)
  - Dowdy, Lewis, 1975 January 21; 26
    - Lewis Dowdy, transcripts and notes (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Lewis Dowdy, compact disc use copy (Box 10, Data-cd RL00207-CD-0209)
  - Edmonds, Ed, Undated; 27
    - Ed Edmonds, transcripts and notes (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Ed Edmonds, compact disc use copy (Box 10, Data-cd RL00207-CD-0209)
  - Elam, Jack, Undated; 28
    - Jack Elam, Side A and B, audiocassette original (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00207-CS-0013)
    - Jack Elam, transcripts and notes (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Jack Elam, compact disc use copy (Box 10, Data-cd RL00207-CD-0209)
    - Jack Elam, 1 of 1, compact disc use copy (Box 9, Audio-cd RL00207-CD-0149)
  - English, Ike, 1974 October 04; 29
    - Ike English, Side A, audiocassette original (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00207-CS-0014)
    - Ike English, 1 of 1, compact disc use copy (Box 9, Audio-cd RL00207-CD-0150)
  - Equal Time guest appearance, Undated; 30
    - Equal Time Chafe guest appearence, Side A, audiocassette original (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00207-CS-0080)
  - Evans, George, Undated; 31
    - George Evans, Side A and B, audiocassette original (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00207-CS-0015)
    - George Evans, transcripts and notes (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - George Evans, compact disc use copy (Box 10, Data-cd RL00207-CD-0209)
    - George Evans, 1 of 1, compact disc use copy (Box 9, Audio-cd RL00207-CD-0151)
  - Faulkener, Mr. and Mrs. Waldo, 1972 July 19; 32
    - Mr. and Mrs. Waldo Faulkener, transcripts and notes (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Mr. and Mrs. Waldo Faulkener, compact disc use copy (Box 10, Data-cd RL00207-CD-0209)
  - Flora, Joe, 1974 September 25; 33
    - Joe Flora, Side A and B, audiocassette original (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00207-CS-0083)
    - Joe Flora, transcripts and notes (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Joe Flora, compact disc use copy (Box 10, Data-cd RL00207-CD-0210)
  - Ford, Robert, 1977 June 17; 34
    - Robert Ford, Side A and B, audiocassette original (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00207-CS-0016)
    - Robert Ford, transcripts and notes (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Robert Ford, compact disc use copy (Box 10, Data-cd RL00207-CD-0210)
    - Robert Ford, 1 of 2, compact disc use copy (Box 9, Audio-cd RL00207-CD-0152)
    - Robert Ford, 2 of 2, compact disc use copy (Box 9, Audio-cd RL00207-CD-0153)
  - Ford, S. N., Undated; 35
    - S. N. Ford, transcripts and notes (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - S. N. Ford, compact disc use copy (Box 10, Data-cd RL00207-CD-0210)
  - Foster, John, 1973 February 14, 1973 October 19; 36
    - John Foster, transcripts and notes (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - John Foster, compact disc use copy (Box 10, Data-cd RL00207-CD-0210)
  - Foster, John, 1973 February 14; 37
    - John Foster, 1 of 2, audiocassette original (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00207-CS-0017)
    - John Foster, 1 of 2, compact disc use copy (Box 9, Audio-cd RL00207-CD-0154)
  - Foster, John, 1973 February 19; 38
    - John Foster, 2 of 2, audiocassette original (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00207-CS-0018)
    - John Foster, 2 of 2, compact disc use copy (Box 9, Audio-cd RL00207-CD-0155)
  - Gardner, Plato, 1977 May 26; 39
    - Plato Gardner, Side A, audiocassette original (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00207-CS-0019)
    - Plato Gardner, transcripts and notes (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Plato Gardner, compact disc use copy (Box 10, Data-cd RL00207-CD-0210)
    - Plato Gardner, 1 of 2, compact disc use copy (Box 9, Audio-cd RL00207-CD-0157)
    - Plato Gardner, 1 of 1, compact disc use copy (Box 9, Audio-cd RL00207-CD-0156)
  - Greensboro Chamber of Commerce notes, Undated; 41
    - Greensboro Chamber of Commerce notes, Side A, audiocassette original (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00207-CS-0077)
  - Greensboro Chamber of Commerce publication notes, Undated; 40
    - Greensboro Chamber of Commerce publication notes, Side B, audiocassette original (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00207-CS-0014)
  - Hairston, Otis, 1972 July 17; 42
    - Otis Hairston, transcripts and notes (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Hairston, Otis, 1977; 43
    - Otis Hairston, Side A and B, audiocassette original (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00207-CS-0020)
    - Otis Hairston, transcripts and notes (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Otis Hairston, 1 of 1, compact disc use copy (Box 9, Audio-cd RL00207-CD-0159)
  - Hairston, Otis, 1972 July 17, 1977; 44
    - Otis Hairston, compact disc use copy (Box 10, Data-cd RL00207-CD-0210)
  - House, W. A., Undated; 45
    - W. A. House, transcripts and notes (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - W. A. House, compact disc use copy (Box 10, Data-cd RL00207-CD-0210)
  - Hudgins, D. E., 1972 July 06; 46
    - D. Edward Hudgins, transcripts and notes (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - D. Edward Hudgins, compact disc use copy (Box 10, Data-cd RL00207-CD-0210)
  - Hudgins, Eula, 1974 December 17; 47
    - Eula Hudgins, transcripts and notes (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - Eula Hudgins, compact disc use copy (Box 10, Data-cd RL00207-CD-0210)
  - Hudgins, Robert E., 1977 May 19; 48
    - Robert E. Hudgins, Side A, audiocassette original (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00207-CS-0021)
    - Robert E. Hudgins, transcripts and notes (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Robert E. Hudgins, compact disc use copy (Box 10, Data-cd RL00207-CD-0208)
    - Robert E. Hudgins, 1 of 2, compact disc use copy (Box 9, Audio-cd RL00207-CD-0161)
  - Jackson, William, 1977 July 12; 49
    - William Jackson, Side A and B, audiocassette original (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00207-CS-0022)
    - William Jackson, transcripts and notes (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - William Jackson, compact disc use copy (Box 10, Data-cd RL00207-CD-0211)
    - William Jackson, 1 of 1, compact disc use copy (Box 9, Audio-cd RL00207-CD-0163)
  - Jacobs, Sol, 1977 December; 50
    - Sol Jacobs, Side A and B, audiocassette original (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00207-CS-0023)
    - Sol Jacobs, 1 of 1, compact disc use copy (Box 9, Audio-cd RL00207-CD-0164)
  - Jarrett, Hobart, Undated; 51
    - Hobart Jarrett, transcripts and notes (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - Hobart Jarrett, compact disc use copy (Box 10, Data-cd RL00207-CD-0211)
  - Johnson, Nelson, 1978 October 24; 52
    - Nelson Johnson, transcripts and notes (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - Nelson Johnson, compact disc use copy (Box 10, Data-cd RL00207-CD-0211)
  - Johnson, Nelson, Undated; 53
    - Nelson Johnson, Side A and B, audiocassette original (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00207-CS-0024)
    - Nelson Johnson, Side A and B, audiocassette original (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00207-CS-0082)
    - Nelson Johnson, Side B, audiocassette original (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00207-CS-0025)
    - Nelson Johnson, Side B, audiocassette original (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00207-CS-0035)
    - Nelson Johnson, 1 of 2, compact disc use copy (Box 9, Audio-cd RL00207-CD-0167)
    - Nelson Johnson, 2 of 2, compact disc use copy (Box 9, Audio-cd RL00207-CD-0168)
    - Nelson Johnson, 1 of 2, compact disc use copy (Box 9, Audio-cd RL00207-CD-0169)
    - Nelson Johnson, 2 of 2, compact disc use copy (Box 10, Audio-cd RL00207-CD-0170)
  - Johnson, Nelson, 1978 September 24; 54
    - Nelson Johnson, 1 of 2, compact disc use copy (Box 9, Audio-cd RL00207-CD-0165)
    - Nelson Johnson, 2 of 2, compact disc use copy (Box 9, Audio-cd RL00207-CD-0166)
  - Johnson, Nelson, 1978 September 12; 55
  - Johnson, Walter, Undated; 56
    - Walter Johnson, Side A, audiocassette original (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00207-CS-0025)
    - Walter Johnson, 1 of 1, compact disc use copy (Box 10, Audio-cd RL00207-CD-0171)
  - Jones, Mrs. David, Undated; 57
    - Mrs. David Jones, Side A and B, audiocassette original (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00207-CS-0026)
    - Mrs. David Jones, transcripts and notes (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - Mrs. David Jones, compact disc use copy (Box 10, Data-cd RL00207-CD-0211)
    - Mrs. David Jones, 1 of 1, compact disc use copy (Box 10, Audio-cd RL00207-CD-0172)
    - Mrs. David Jones, 1 of 1, compact disc use copy (Box 10, Audio-cd RL00207-CD-0206)
  - Kilimanjaro, John Marshall Stephenson, Undated; 58
    - John Marshall Stephenson Kilimanjaro, transcripts and notes (Box 2, Folder 39)
    - John Marshall Stephenson Kilimanjaro, compact disc use copy (Box 10, Data-cd RL00207-CD-0211)
  - Knox, Joe, 1977 June 17; 59
    - Joe Knox, Side A and B, audiocassette original (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00207-CS-0027)
    - Joe Knox, transcripts and notes (Box 2, Folder 40)
    - Joe Knox, compact disc use copy (Box 10, Data-cd RL00207-CD-0211)
    - Joe Knox, 1 of 2, compact disc use copy (Box 10, Audio-cd RL00207-CD-0173)
    - Joe Knox, 2 of 2, compact disc use copy (Box 10, Audio-cd RL00207-CD-0174)
  - Lewis, John, Undated; 60
    - John Lewis, transcripts and notes (Box 2, Folder 41)
    - John Lewis, compact disc use copy (Box 10, Data-cd RL00207-CD-0211)
  - Lineberry, Al, 1974 December 17; 61
    - Al Lineberry, transcripts and notes (Box 2, Folder 43)
    - Al Lineberry, compact disc use copy (Box 10, Data-cd RL00207-CD-0211)
  - Linek, R. B., Undated; 62
    - R. B. Linek, transcripts and notes (Box 2, Folder 42)
    - R. B. Linek, compact disc use copy (Box 10, Data-cd RL00207-CD-0211)
  - Mark, Carolyn, 1974 October 10; 63
    - Carolyn Mark, transcripts and notes (Box 2, Folder 44)
    - Carolyn Mark, compact disc use copy (Box 10, Data-cd RL00207-CD-0211)
  - McCoy, Cleo, 1977 September 06; 64
    - Cleo McCoy, transcripts and notes (Box 2, Folder 45)
    - Cleo McCoy, compact disc use copy (Box 10, Data-cd RL00207-CD-0211)
  - McNeill, Joseph, 1978; 65
    - Joseph McNeill, Side A and B, audiocassette original (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00207-CS-0028)
    - Joseph McNeill, transcripts and notes (Box 2, Folder 46)
    - Joseph McNeill, compact disc use copy (Box 10, Data-cd RL00207-CD-0212)
    - Joseph McNeill, 1 of 1, compact disc use copy (Box 10, Audio-cd RL00207-CD-0175)
  - Morehead, David, 1974 December 19; 66
    - David Morehead, transcripts and notes (Box 2, Folder 47)
    - David Morehead, compact disc use copy (Box 10, Data-cd RL00207-CD-0212)
  - Oakes, Mr. and Mrs. David, 1977 December; 67
    - Mr. and Mrs. David Oakes, Side A and B, audiocassette original (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00207-CS-0029)
    - Mr. and Mrs. David Oakes, 2 of 2, compact disc use copy (Box 10, Audio-cd RL00207-CD-0176)
  - Parker, Mrs. Franklin, Undated; 68
    - Mrs. Franklin Parker, Side A and B, audiocassette original (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00207-CS-0030)